

CONTACT ME AT

- New Shah Shams Colony Multan.Pakistan
- zohaibhassan7870@gmail.com
- zohaib zebi
- +92 302 7870 765

SKILLS SUMMARY

- •••• Adobe Photoshop cc
- •••• Adobe Illustrator cc
- •••• Adobe XD
- •••• Corel Draw
- •••• In Page

ZOHAIB HASSAN

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a graphic designer with a strong background. One year of experience in graphic design, web design, mobile application design, web banner design, logo design, Facebook ad creation, and much more to learn and work for a software company.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Graphic Design

TexBax | Oct 2020 - present

 A graphic design student working at an entry level in a software company. Passionate about web and UX / UI design. Experience creating many websites, e-commerce and mobile apps, website design in the current company.

UI/UX Designer

TecBax | Oct 2020 - present

- Managing complex projects from start to finish.
- Collaborate with other designers.
- Translating needs into polished, high-end designs.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Garrison Grammar Higher Secondary School Matric | 2014 - 2015

Garrison Grammar Higher Secondary School

Intermediate | 2018 - 2019

- Minor in Management
- Thesis involved studying several technology companies and optimizing their product design process

LANGUAGES

- Urdu
- English